We set up a fashion C&D and C&M major
It is also the only major in China
I feel that it is very convenient
But this software saves a lot of unnecessary and complicated steps
I also really want to learn this software
This software is really convenient for our fashion design
Because there is no need to make food
It can have the same effect as food
It also saves people and costs
This software is really worth learning
The cloud system still has its own very good characteristics
The first one is that it is very fast
The effect is also very fast and can be presented to the user
The second one is that it is very advantageous in terms of the whole virtual market
So at present, after we cooperate with the company
After the whole teaching system is pushed to this software
It should be very good for students to reflect